James Kolbe Papers, 1958-2006 (bulk 1985-2006)
University of Arizona Libraries, Special Collections
- Subgroup 3: Media Files, 1958-2008
  - Series 1: Photographic Materials, 1958-2008
    - Subseries 1: Photographs, 1958-2008
      - Events, El Coronado, Safford Main Street Glenbar Gin Tour, October 14, 1992 (Box 200, Folder 82)
      - Events, Elected Officials Brunch, June 5, 1994 (Box 200, Folder 83)
      - Events, Election Night, November 3, 1992 (Box 200, Folder 84)
      - Events, Election Night, 1994 (Box 200, Folder 85)
      - Events, The European Institute Seminar, March 11, 1997 (Box 200, Folder 86)
      - Events, Expo Maquila Acapulco, December 5, 1986 (Box 200, Folder 87)
      - Events, F-16 Flight with Arizona Air Guard, 1986 (Box 200, Folder 88)
      - Events, F-16 Shoot, undated (Box 200, Folder 89)
      - Events, Factory and Store visits, ca. 1985-ca. 2005 (Box 201, Folder 1)
      - Events, Factory visits, 1990-1991 (Box 201, Folder 2)
      - Events, Flag Dedication, Green Valley, Arizona, 1986 (Box 201, Folder 3)
      - Events, Flood relief, 1983 (Box 201, Folder 4)
      - Events, Food Bank Tucson, 1985 (Box 201, Folder 5)
      - Events, Food Plus visit, March 6, 1987 (Box 201, Folder 6)
      - Events, Food Plus visit, undated (Box 201, Folder 7)
      - Events, Forest Service Ribbon Cutting, 1999 (Box 201, Folder 8)
      - Events, Fort Bowie visit, August 12, 1987 (Box 201, Folder 9)
      - Events, Fort Devens Tour, undated (Box 201, Folder 10)
      - Events, Fort Huachuca Fire visit, undated (Box 201, Folder 11)
      - Events, Fort Huachuca visit, undated (Box 201, Folder 12)
      - Events, Fort Huachuca World War II Buildings News Conference, June 19, 1987 (Box 201, Folder 13)
      - Events, Freevibe.com speech, undated (Box 201, Folder 14)
      - Events, Freedom Park at Davis Monthan Air Force Base, 1986 (Box 201, Folder 15)
      - Events, Friendship Village, June 28, 1986 (Box 201, Folder 16)
      - Events, Fundraiser in Sierra Vista, Arizona, undated (Box 201, Folder 17)
      - Events, Gen Folks Protesting, ca. August 22, 1994 (Box 201, Folder 18)
      - Events, General (1 of 2), 1984-2001 (Box 201, Folder 19)
      - Events, General (2 of 2), 1984-2001 (Box 201, Folder 20)
      - Events, General, 2002-2004 (Box 201, Folder 21)
      - Events, General Electric Batteries visit, September 11, 1987 (Box 201, Folder 22)
      - Events, General Motors Inland visit, September 11, 1987 (Box 201, Folder 23)
      - Events, Genoa Expo, 1992 (Box 201, Folder 24)
      - Events, Goodwill opening, April 21, 1995 (Box 201, Folder 25)
      - Events, Gospel Rescue Mission Annual Meal Service, December 3, 1999 (Box 201, Folder 26)
      - Events, Governor Symington signs Hughes Incentive Bill, July 7, 1992 (Box 201, Folder 27)
      - Events, GOP Retreat, 1991 (Box 201, Folder 28)
      - Events, Greater Phoenix Black Chamber of Commerce, 1999 (Box 201, Folder 29)
      - Events, Greater Phoenix Economic Council, May 8, 2000 (Box 201, Folder 30)
      - Events, Green Valley Flag Dedication, 1986 (Box 201, Folder 31)
      - Events, Green Valley Parade, ca. October 29, 1994 (Box 201, Folder 32)
      - Events, Green Valley Town Hall and Breakfast, undated (Box 201, Folder 33)
      - Events, Green Valley Town Hall State of the District and INS Tour, Florence, 1987 (Box 201, Folder 34)
      - Events, Halloween, ca. October 31, 1994 (Box 201, Folder 35)
      - Events, Hannoi/Saigon meetings and Vietnam street scenes, ca. 1991 (Box 201, Folder 36)
      - Events, Harquahala Valley Irrigation District visit, May 22, 1985 (Box 201, Folder 37)
      - Events, Health Care Fraud Forum, February 10, 1993 (Box 201, Folder 38)
      - Events, Historic Kolbe, undated (Box 201, Folder 39)
      - Events, Hong Kong Handover, June 30, 1997 (Box 201, Folder 40)
      - Events, Hope News Conference, August 1, 1992 (Box 201, Folder 41)
      - Events, House Fix Up for Lilly Cox, October 17, 1992 (Box 201, Folder 42)
      - Events, Imus KTUC Radio, May 5, 1996 (Box 201, Folder 43)
      - Events, Interior Tour, 1991 (Box 201, Folder 44)
      - Events, IBM meeting with Japanese journalists, May, 1989 (Box 201, Folder 45)
      - Events, IBM visit, 1987 (Box 201, Folder 46)
      - Events, Interparliamentary meeting in Savannah, December 20, 1999 (Box 201, Folder 47)
      - Events, IRI visit, 2000 (Box 201, Folder 48)
      - Events, Israel '84/Japan '87, 1984-1987 (Box 201, Folder 49)
      - Events, Japan-American Society of Tucson meeting, November, 1987 (Box 201, Folder 50)
      - Events, Joint Press Conference with Kyl, ca. 2002 (Box 201, Folder 51)
      - Events, Kasich Luncheon, September 24, 1994 (Box 201, Folder 52)
      - Events, Kitt Peak visit, undated (Box 201, Folder 53)
      - Events, Kolbe and children, ca. 1992 (Box 201, Folder 54)
      - Events, Kolbe at McDonald's, 1994 (Box 201, Folder 55)
      - Events, Kolbe at Opening Day of Spring Training, March 7, 1992 (Box 201, Folder 56)
      - Events, Kolbe at Saguaro News Conference, February, 1992 (Box 201, Folder 57)
      - Events, Kolbe Birthday, undated (Box 201, Folder 58)
      - Events, Kolbe Budget Workshop, February 8, 1993 (Box 201, Folder 59)
      - Events, Kolbe Council, ca. 1994 (Box 201, Folder 60)
      - Events, Kolbe Election party, 1998 (Box 201, Folder 61)
      - Events, Kolbe Golf Tournament, 2004 (Box 201, Folder 62)
      - Events, Kolbe in Parade, undated (Box 201, Folder 63)
      - Events, John Kolbe wedding, undated (Box 201, Folder 64)
      - Events, Kolbe/Quayle visit to Modular Mining, March 16, 1992 (Box 201, Folder 65)
      - Events, Kolbe tours Sabino Canyon Flood damage, January 17, 1993 (Box 201, Folder 66)
      - Events, Kolbe with Children, 1986-1992 (Box 201, Folder 67)
      - Events, Kolbe Youth News Conference at Territorial, March 14, 1992 (Box 201, Folder 68)
      - Events, Kolbe's 58th Birthday party, undated (Box 201, Folder 69)
      - Events, Susan G. Komen Race for the Cure, 1999 (Box 201, Folder 70)
      - Events, KRQ Christmas Carol and Kolbe as "Uncle Fred", December 18, 1992 (Box 201, Folder 71)
      - Events, KTAR Radio Show and Salvation Army bell ringing, December, 1992 (Box 201, Folder 72)
      - Events, Kyl Day University of Arizona visit, ca. September 14, 1994 (Box 201, Folder 73)
      - Events, Labor Day Parade, 2000 (Box 201, Folder 74)
      - Events, Labor Day at Cabin, undated (Box 201, Folder 75)
      - Events, Land Exchange meetings, ca. 1987 (Box 201, Folder 76)
      - Events, Larry Craig Breakfast, undated (Box 201, Folder 77)
      - Events, Law Enforcement Training Speech, undated (Box 201, Folder 78)
      - Events, Love of Reading Week, February, 1987 (Box 201, Folder 79)
      - Events, Magellan Circle Dinner, March 22, 2005 (Box 201, Folder 80)
      - Events, Mammoth Town Hall, 1985 (Box 201, Folder 81)
      - Evetns, Marana Town Hall, 1985 (Box 201, Folder 82)
      - Events, Mecham Inauguration, January 5, 1987 (Box 201, Folder 83)
      - Events, Meeting Carlos Cruz, 1998 (Box 201, Folder 84)
      - Events, Meeting with Business Financial Development Corporation, July, 1992 (Box 201, Folder 85)
      - Events, Meeting with Clergy, undated (Box 201, Folder 86)
      - Events, Meeting with Governor Rodolfo Felix Valdez, January 5, 1987 (Box 201, Folder 87)
      - Events, Meeting with Representative Romeo Caballero in District of Columbia, March 10, 1987 (Box 201, Folder 88)
      - Events, Meeting with Russian representatives, 2000 (Box 201, Folder 89)
      - Events, Meetings with Labor Industry Coalition and Trade Task Force, July 25, 1985 (Box 201, Folder 90)
      - Events, Medicare Hearing- Tucson, 1985 (Box 202, Folder 1)
      - Events, Mideast Trip, 1986 (Box 202, Folder 2)
      - Events, MOWW Passing of the Colors, undated (Box 202, Folder 3)
      - Events, Military Visit with Jon Kyl, undated (Box 202, Folder 4)
      - Events, Miracle Network Telethon, 1987 (Box 202, Folder 5)
      - Events, Mount Graham Visit, undated (Box 202, Folder 6)
      - Events, Noco Maquila, September, 1987 (Box 202, Folder 7)
      - Events, Nacozari Smelter Dedication, June, 1986 (Box 202, Folder 8)
      - Events, Nagoya Japan Cactus and Freedom Shrine, February, 1987 (Box 202, Folder 9)
      - Events, NASDAQ opening, March 8, 2002 (Box 202, Folder 10)
      - Events, Meeting NCAA Basketball Championship Team at White House, 1997 (Box 202, Folder 11)
      - Events, National Day of Excellence, undated (Box 202, Folder 12)
      - Events, National Symphony Orchestra's American Residency in Arizona visit, May, 1997 (Box 202, Folder 13)
      - Events, North American Free Trade Agreement, 1993 (Box 202, Folder 14)
      - Events, Oktoberfest, 1985 (Box 202, Folder 15)
      - Events, Open House, February 18, 2002 (Box 202, Folder 16)
      - Events, Office Retreat, January 3, 2004 (Box 202, Folder 17)
      - Events, Out County visits, 2000 (Box 202, Folder 18)
      - Events, Palo Verde Kiwanis Club Pancake Feed, October 7, 1984 (Box 202, Folder 19)
      - Events, National Summit on Retirement Savings, June 17, 1998 (Box 202, Folder 20)
      - Events, Parade, undated (Box 202, Folder 21)
      - Events, Patagonia 4th of July, 1985 (Box 202, Folder 22)
      - Events, Patagonia Town Hall, 1985 (Box 202, Folder 23)
      - Events, Pearl Harbor Medal Ceremony at Fort Lowell Park, February 29, 1992 (Box 202, Folder 24)
      - Events, Philadelphia Log Cabin Speech, November 15, 1997 (Box 202, Folder 25)
      - Events, Phoenix Event, April 17, 1994 (Box 202, Folder 26)
      - Events, Picnic with Constituents, undated (Box 202, Folder 27)
      - Events, Pilliod News Conference, July 25, 1987 (Box 202, Folder 28)
      - Events, Postal Inspection Service, undated (Box 202, Folder 29)
      - Events, Pre-Election Rally, November 6, 1994 (Box 202, Folder 30)
      - Events, Presentation of Flowing Wells Judges Merit Award, undated (Box 202, Folder 31)
      - Events, Primary Election Night, September 8, 1992 (Box 202, Folder 32)
      - Events, Primary Night, undated (Box 202, Folder 33)
      - Events, Princeton Conference, March, 1991 (Box 202, Folder 34)
      - Events, Public Lands Information Center, 2000 (Box 202, Folder 35)
      - Events, Post-Election visits, ca. 1985 (Box 202, Folder 36)
      - Events, Procurement Conference, May, 1987 (Box 202, Folder 37)
      - Events, Project Employees Recreation Association speech, 1985 (Box 202, Folder 38)
      - Events, Radio Bush Fundraiser, August 12, 2000 (Box 202, Folder 39)
      - Events, Raise the Roof Celebration, October 16, 1999 (Box 202, Folder 40)
      - Events, Rehab Institute of Tucson Wheelchair Scavenger Hunt, July 16, 1992 (Box 202, Folder 41)
      - Events, Retirement and Assisted Living Facilities speech, June, 2000 (Box 202, Folder 42)
      - Events, Ribbon Cutting Marana Health Center, May, 2000 (Box 202, Folder 43)
      - Events, Rillito River Bank Tour, September, 1986 (Box 202, Folder 44)
      - Events, Rillito River Flood Control Project Ground Breaking Ceremony, July 13, 1995 (Box 202, Folder 45)
      - Events, River Hearing and Habitat for Humanity, February 13, 1993-February 19, 1993 (Box 202, Folder 46)
      - Events, Roof Raising Ceremony, February 28, 1999 (Box 202, Folder 47)
      - Events, Russian Visit/Labor Day Parade, 2000 (Box 202, Folder 48)
      - Events, Salvation Army, Food Bank, Sabino Canyon, 1992-1993 (Box 202, Folder 49)
      - Events, Safford, Tucson, Patagonia State of the District, January, 1987 (Box 202, Folder 50)
      - Events, Safford CU visit, 2000 (Box 202, Folder 51)
      - Events, Safford Cotton Tour, August 30, 1992 (Box 202, Folder 52)
      - Events, Safford Multi-Use Path Development, April, 2000 (Box 202, Folder 53)
      - Events, Safford State of the District speech, undated (Box 202, Folder 54)
      - Events, Safford Town Hall, undated (Box 202, Folder 55)
      - Events, Saguaro National Monument, undated (Box 202, Folder 56)
      - Events, Saguaro Park Expansion Celebration, July 18, 1999 (Box 202, Folder 57)
      - Events, Salute to Congress, September 17, 1985 (Box 202, Folder 58)
      - Events, San Pedro Riparian Area Spring Visit with Jack Williams, 1986 (Box 202, Folder 59)
      - Events, Savoy Opera House, 1984 (Box 202, Folder 60)
      - Events, Scottsdale Rotary Club Jewish National Fund Dinner, 1989 (Box 202, Folder 61)
      - Events, Scottsdale Rotar Club speech, undated (Box 202, Folder 62)
      - Events, Sedona Trip, undated (Box 202, Folder 63)
      - Events, The Seniors Coalition to Save Medicare, July, 1995 (Box 202, Folder 64)
      - Events, Shakespeare Theatre Company Congressional Night, April, 2006 (Box 202, Folder 65)
      - Events, Sierra Vista Day and Town Hall, undated (Box 202, Folder 66)
      - Events, Sierra Vista Home Health Care Hearing, 1986 (Box 202, Folder 67)
      - Events, Sierra Vista Town Hall, undated (Box 202, Folder 68)
      - Events, Sleeping Bag N/C at Rincon, September 21, 1992 (Box 202, Folder 69)
      - Events, Softball Game, ca. September 17, 1994 (Box 202, Folder 70)
      - Events, Solar Car Presentation, August 29, 2001 (Box 202, Folder 71)
      - Events, SRP PIC Luncheon, June 30, 1989 (Box 202, Folder 72)
      - Events, Southern Arizona AIDS Foundation, 2004 (Box 202, Folder 73)
      - Events, Southern Arizona Home Builders Association Debate with Beehler, August 24, 1992 (Box 202, Folder 74)
      - Events, Springerville Town Hall, 1985 (Box 202, Folder 75)
      - Events, Springerville visit with Mayor D. Silva, 1985 (Box 202, Folder 76)
      - Events, STANDARD Missile-3 Celebration, August 11, 1999 (Box 202, Folder 77)
      - Events, Swearing In, 1985 (Box 202, Folder 78)
      - Events, Swearing In Ceremony, undated (Box 202, Folder 79)
      - Events, Swearing In Party, January, 1985 (Box 202, Folder 80)
      - Events, SXEW PD Tour, November 24, 1987 (Box 202, Folder 81)
      - Events, Teacher for a Day, October 13, 1992 (Box 202, Folder 82)
      - Events, Toers/Kolbe Debate at Amphi, October 19, 1992 (Box 202, Folder 83)
      - Events, Tombstone, ca. 1985 (Box 202, Folder 84)
      - Events, Tour of Boeing Plant, June 30, 1997 (Box 202, Folder 85)
      - Events, Tour of CGHS, 1992 (Box 202, Folder 86)
      - Events, Tourism Industry Unity Dinner, March 15, 1989 (Box 202, Folder 87)
      - Events, Toys for Tots University Medical Center Distribution, undated (Box 202, Folder 88)
      - Events, Transatlantic Policy Network Mid-Year Assessment, 1999 (Box 202, Folder 89)
      - Events, Tucson Chamber of Commerce and Cox Communications speech, undated (Box 202, Folder 90)
      - Events, Tucson Community Food Bank, undated (Box 202, Folder 91)
      - Events, Tucson Fire Department Tour, undated (Box 202, Folder 92)
      - Events, Tucson Medial Center Tour, 1987-1992 (Box 202, Folder 93)
      - Events, Tucson Naval Reserve Retirement Ceremony, March 11, 1989 (Box 202, Folder 94)
      - Events, Tucson Police Department Evidence Room Tour, 1992 (Box 202, Folder 95)
      - Events, Tucson Sanitation Workers visit, November 5, 1986 (Box 202, Folder 96)
      - Events, Tucson Town Hall, State of the District, Foster Parents Fair, undated (Box 202, Folder 97)
      - Events, Tucson Town Hall meeting, 1985 (Box 202, Folder 98)
      - Events, Tucson Town Hall with Donnelly, April 11, 1987 (Box 202, Folder 99)
      - Events, Tucson Town Halls, July, 1994 (Box 202, Folder 100)
      - Events, Tucson Wilderness Forum, undated (Box 202, Folder 101)
      - Events, Turkey Walk-Off, December 6, 1999 (Box 203, Folder 1)
      - Events, United States Customs Seizure News Conference, October 30, 1992 (Box 203, Folder 2)
      - Events, United States Ship Arizona Memorial Service, December, 2000 (Box 203, Folder 3)
      - Events, University of Arizona Homecoming, 2007 (Box 203, Folder 4)
      - Events, University of Arizona/University Medical Center Heart Tour, July 27, 1987 (Box 203, Folder 5)
      - Events, USAID Trip, undated (Box 203, Folder 6)
      - Events, Vatican Observatory Dedication, October 20, 1993 (Box 203, Folder 7)
      - Events, Velcro International visit with Bob Fernandez in Douglas, Arizona, 1985 (Box 203, Folder 8)
      - Events, VA visit, undated (Box 203, Folder 9)
      - Events, VFW, 1986 (Box 203, Folder 10)
      - Events, Vietnam Veterans Parade, undated (Box 203, Folder 11)
      - Events, Visit to United States Air Force Academy, ca. 2008 (Box 203, Folder 12)
      - Events, Visit to United States Military Academy, May, 2003 (Box 203, Folder 13)
      - Events, Visit to United States Naval Academy, 2005 (Box 203, Folder 14)
      - Events, Visit with Border Patrol Agents, October 10, 1989 (Box 203, Folder 15)
      - Events, Washington Council on International Trade, June 30, 1997 (Box 203, Folder 16)
      - Events, Watchdogs of the Treasury, ca. 1986-1990 (Box 203, Folder 17)
      - Events, West Gila Valley Events, 1980 (Box 203, Folder 18)
      - Events, Western Army Aviation Training Site, May 29, 1993 (Box 203, Folder 19)
      - Events, Wild West, undated (Box 203, Folder 20)
      - Events, Willcox Apple Tour and Lee Gernigan Ranch visit, August, 1987 (Box 203, Folder 21)
      - Events, Willcox Rex Allen Days, ca. October 1, 1994 (Box 203, Folder 22)
      - Events, Willcox Tomato Greenhouse Tour, October 14, 1992 (Box 203, Folder 23)
      - Events, Willcox Town Hall, undated (Box 203, Folder 24)
      - Events, Women's Business Conference, May, 1986 (Box 203, Folder 25)
      - Events, World Economic Forum, undated (Box 203, Folder 26)
      - Events, Wrigley Mansion Phoenix visits, 1988 (Box 203, Folder 27)
      - Events, Yellow Gin Tour in Stanfield, October 28, 1992 (Box 203, Folder 28)
      - Events, Yaqui Indians in Marana, 1985 (Box 203, Folder 29)
      - Events, Youth Advisory Council, March, 1987 (Box 203, Folder 30)
      - Fort Huachuca and Wooden Buildings EPG Ground Breaking, June 19, 1987 (Box 203, Folder 31)
      - General (1 of 2), 1985-2002 (Box 203, Folder 32)
      - General (2 of 2), 1985-2002 (Box 203, Folder 33)
      - General (1 of 18), undated (Box 203, Folder 34)
      - General (2 of 18), undated (Box 203, Folder 35)
      - General (3 of 18), undated (Box 203, Folder 36)
      - General (4 of 18), undated (Box 203, Folder 37)
      - General (5 of 18), undated (Box 203, Folder 38)
      - General (6 of 18), undated (Box 203, Folder 39)
      - General (7 of 18), undated (Box 203, Folder 40)
      - General (8 of 18), undated (Box 203, Folder 41)
      - General (9 of 18), undated (Box 203, Folder 42)
      - General (10 of 18), undated (Box 203, Folder 43)
      - General (11 of 18), undated (Box 203, Folder 44)
      - General (12 of 18), undated (Box 203, Folder 45)
      - General (13 of 18), undated (Box 203, Folder 46)
      - General (14 of 18), undated (Box 204, Folder 1)
      - General (15 of 18), undated (Box 204, Folder 2)
      - General (16 of 18), undated (Box 204, Folder 3)
      - General (17 of 18), undated (Box 204, Folder 4)
      - General (18 of 18), undated (Box 204, Folder 5)
      - General, Contact Sheets (1 of 3), undated (Box 204, Folder 6)
      - General, Contact Sheets (2 of 3), undated (Box 204, Folder 7)
      - General, Contact Sheets (3 of 3), undated (Box 204, Folder 8)
      - General, Military related photos, 1988 (Box 204, Folder 9)
      - General, Military related photos, 1993 (Box 204, Folder 10)
      - General, Police related photos, undated (Box 204, Folder 11)
      - General, Rural Metro related photos, undated (Box 204, Folder 12)
      - General, Vietnam Memorial, undated (Box 204, Folder 13)
      - General, Women's Photos, undated (Box 204, Folder 14)
      - GOTV Rally, September 6, 1992 (Box 204, Folder 15)
      - Green Valley Town Hall, 1985 (Box 204, Folder 16)
      - Joe Hruby Medal, May 2, 1987 (Box 204, Folder 17)
      - Kearny, 1985 (Box 204, Folder 18)
      - Promotional Material, Kolbe as Congressional Page, ca. 1958-ca. 1960 (Box 204, Folder 19)
      - Kolbe, Group Shots, ca. 1985-ca. 1993 (Box 204, Folder 20)
      - Kolbe, Portraits, ca. 1985 (Box 204, Folder 21)
      - Kolbe Promotional Shots (1 of 2), 1984-2005 (Box 204, Folder 22)
      - Kolbe Promotional Shots (2 of 2), 1984-2005 (Box 204, Folder 23)
      - Mount Graham Tour, October, 1986 (Box 204, Folder 24)
      - Naco Sewage visit, 1986 (Box 204, Folder 25)
      - Pages, undated (Box 204, Folder 26)
      - Personal, Family photos, undated (Box 204, Folder 27)
      - Personal, General, 1992 (Box 204, Folder 28)
      - Sierra Vista Town Hall, 1985 (Box 204, Folder 29)
      - Slide Show, 1994 (Box 204, Folder 30)
      - Staff (1 of 3), 1985-1989 (Box 204, Folder 31)
      - Staff (2 of 3), 1985-1989 (Box 204, Folder 32)
      - Staff (3 of 3), 1985-1989 (Box 204, Folder 33)
      - Staff (1 of 2), 1991-1996 (Box 204, Folder 34)
      - Staff (2 of 2), 1991-1996 (Box 204, Folder 35)
      - Staff (1 of 2), 2000-2005 (Box 204, Folder 36)
      - Staff (2 of 2), 2000-2005 (Box 205, Folder 1)
      - Staff, undated (Box 205, Folder 2)
      - Staff, Page Adam Kuasman, ca. 2000 (Box 205, Folder 3)
      - Staff, Staff Christmas Party, 1996 (Box 205, Folder 4)
      - Tombstone Breakfast/Bisbee Town Hall, undated (Box 205, Folder 5)
      - Tour of Troop Quarters at Old Buena High School, undated (Box 205, Folder 6)
      - Travel, Africa, undated (Box 205, Folder 7)
      - Travel, Africa Congressional Delegation (1 of 2), August, 1997 (Box 205, Folder 8)
      - Travel, Africa Congressional Delegation (2 of 2), August, 1997 (Box 205, Folder 9)
      - Travel, Africa Cote d'Ivoire (1 of 3), August, 1997 (Box 205, Folder 10)
      - Travel, Africa Cote d'Ivoire (2 of 3), August, 1997 (Box 205, Folder 11)
      - Travel, Africa Cote d'Ivoire (3 of 3), August, 1997 (Box 205, Folder 12)
      - Travel, Amerasian Center, ca. 1991 (Box 205, Folder 13)
      - Travel, Aravaipa Canyon, September 2, 1987 (Box 205, Folder 14)
      - Travel, Cambodia and Thailand, ca. 1991 (Box 205, Folder 15)
      - Travel, Casa Grande, Florence, Safford, and Duncan, Arizona, January, 1987 (Box 205, Folder 16)
      - Travel, Central America Trip, November 10, 1998 (Box 205, Folder 17)
      - Travel, China Congressional Delegation (1 of 3), January 13, 1997-January 17, 1997 (Box 205, Folder 18)
      - Travel, China Congressional Delegation (2 of 3), January 13, 1997-January 17, 1997 (Box 205, Folder 19)
      - Travel, China Congressional Delegation (3 of 3), January 13, 1997-January 17, 1997 (Box 205, Folder 20)
      - Travel, Congressional Delegation to Afghanistan and Central Asia, January 19, 2002 (Box 205, Folder 21)
      - Travel, Congressional Delegation Crane, 1996 (Box 205, Folder 22)
      - Travel, Congressional Delegation South Korea with Korean President, January, 1999 (Box 205, Folder 23)
      - Travel, Customs and Samsonite in Nogales, Arizona, January, 1987 (Box 205, Folder 24)
      - Travel, El Paso, Texas Customs, September 11, 1987 (Box 205, Folder 25)
      - Travel, Florence, Coolidge, and Eloy, Arizona, 1985 (Box 205, Folder 26)
      - Travel, Future of Democracy Beyond the Baltics, Latvia, February, 2004 (Box 205, Folder 27)
      - Travel, General, 1990 (Box 205, Folder 28)
      - Travel, Guam trip, undated (Box 205, Folder 29)
      - Travel, Hanoi trip, undated (Box 205, Folder 30)
      - Travel, Hong Kong Congressional Delegation, January 18, 1996 (Box 205, Folder 31)
      - Travel, Hong Kong trip, October 3, 1997-December 3, 1997 (Box 205, Folder 32)
      - Travel, Japan, August, 1987 (Box 205, Folder 33)
      - Travel, Jordan, undated (Box 205, Folder 34)
      - Travel, Kiev, 1989 (Box 205, Folder 35)
      - Travel, Kosovo, 1999 (Box 205, Folder 36)
      - Travel, Laos, ca. 1991 (Box 205, Folder 37)
      - Travel, Mexico, undated (Box 205, Folder 38)